<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Cute Puppies</string>

    <string name="app_bar_title">Cute\nPuppies</string>

    <string name="cat_breed_header">Breed</string>

    <string name="cat_gender_subtitle">Gender</string>
    <string name="cat_hair_color_subtitle">Hair Color</string>
    <string name="cat_eye_color_subtitle">Eye Color</string>
    <string name="cat_age_subtitle">Age</string>

    <string name="cat_name_lulu">Lulu</string>
    <string name="cat_name_lala">Lala</string>
    <string name="cat_name_dd">DD</string>
    <string name="cat_name_tt">TT</string>
    <string name="cat_name_chuchu">Chuchu</string>
    <string name="cat_name_coco">Coco</string>
    <string name="cat_name_momo">Momo</string>

    <string name="cat_dob_lulu">Jan 11, 2017</string>
    <string name="cat_dob_lala">Dec 6, 2017</string>
    <string name="cat_dob_dd">Jan 15, 2015</string>
    <string name="cat_dob_tt">Jan 15, 2015</string>
    <string name="cat_dob_chuchu">Dec 25, 2016</string>
    <string name="cat_dob_coco">Oct 29, 2016</string>
    <string name="cat_dob_momo">Oct 27, 2016</string>

    <string name="cat_gender_male">Male</string>
    <string name="cat_gender_female">Male</string>

    <string name="cat_description_lulu"><![CDATA[I\'ll be happy & brave cat.]]></string>
    <string name="cat_description_lala">The pretty troublemaker cat.</string>
    <string name="cat_description_dd">Fluffy, chattering, friendly and likes bread.</string>
    <string name="cat_description_tt">The beautiful and Has a Wonderful Meow.</string>
    <string name="cat_description_chuchu">The innocent baby princess.</string>
    <string name="cat_description_coco">The cool, curious, collected handsome doctor cat.</string>
    <string name="cat_description_momo">The iconic Amazing One and only orange chairman.</string>

    <string name="cat_breed_lulu">Munchkin, British ShortHair</string>
    <string name="cat_breed_lala">Long hair Napoleon Munchkin</string>
    <string name="cat_breed_dd">Norwegian Forest</string>
    <string name="cat_breed_tt">American + European ShortHair</string>
    <string name="cat_breed_chuchu">Scottish Fold/Persian Mix</string>
    <string name="cat_breed_coco">Scottish Highland Straight</string>
    <string name="cat_breed_momo">Exotic ShortHair and Tabby</string>

    <string name="cat_about_lulu">
        Lulu is a brown-coated cat with a white muzzle. He has yellow-golden eyes. If you look
        closely, you can see he has an M forehead mark. He has dark-colored paws and unlike the
        other cats, he has a bushy raccoon-shaped tail.
        He is one of the most mischievous, if not THE most mischievous one of all. He is a glutton,
        lunging for whatever treats he can find. He is always very hungry, often meowing loud to ask
        for treats. He often kicks out the other cats out of their comfortable spots.
        He often bites toys intensely during games, mostly dragonfly toys which are hard to pull
        free since Lulu has sharp canines. Although Lulu likes to eat, he refuses to eat meals that
        look scary, like a big prawn or an octopus. Lulu often takes great pride to pick fights with
        other cats in any case, often ending with other cats and him fighting.
    </string>

    <string name="cat_about_lala">
        Lala is an Napoleon Munchkin cat with a long white fur coat. Lala has bright blue eyes and
        a black blotch on her nose and like a Munchkin, she has short legs.
        She is hungry most of the time and even runs to quickly get the food. She also hates to be
        bathed, always trying to run away and meowing very loudly. Lala is a big fan of the cat
        wheel, she is very athletic and goes very fast on the wheel.
        Lala can jump the highest out of all the cats, around 2-3 meters.
        Lala panics the most when bathed. Lala tail is 32cm long.
    </string>

    <string name="cat_about_dd">
        DD is a Norwegian Forest Cat and he likes bread. He is very friendly and gentle as well as
        the fluffiest cat. He has long, creamy brown and white fur. He has bright yellow eyes. Due
        to such a huge coat of fur, many people may think that he is fat, he is actually quite slim.
        DD is very fond of boxes. He also loves pushing things off tables and counter tops such as
        bread. He is the only one who knows how to open cupboards and drawers. Despite being calm
        most of the time, DD can lose his patience. DD meow is a soft chatter. He hisses at any
        machine or toy which looks like a cat.
    </string>

    <string name="cat_about_tt">
        TT is an American Shorthair cat. She is one of the more territorial cats. TT is a tall,
        queenly cat with short, greyish-silver fur and sad olive-green eyes. She also has dark grey
        markings across her fur, which is seen on her head as well. She has a yellow spot on top of
        her nose. TT has a scar on her right eye due to having Feline Herpes when she was kitten,
        which is why the eye appears cloudy. As a kitten, TT was very skinny with a black pattern
        across the bridge of her nose, which indicated how very sick she was. She is very sensitive.
        TT can understand human language and she is very patient as well. She is also a very
        well-mannered lady and waits for her food. She also gets upset easily when she sees unknown
        people or animals. She is a big fan of the cat wheel.
    </string>

    <string name="cat_about_chuchu">
        Chuchu is a tri-colored Highland Fold. Chuchu is a fluffy longhaired cat with a tri-colored
        calico coat. She has bright yellow eyes with dark pupils. She also has a slightly smushed
        appearance to her face. She has a few dark brown, thin stripes on her forehead, small,
        folded ears and has a short, fluffy tail. She is also tall. She overall has more of a white
        fur color. She has an "M" on her forehead. Chuchu is the most timid cat. She has a very
        innocent behavior. Chuchu usually prefers to just sit around, does not take part in most
        of the games, and is very calm, though she can get frightened easily. As Chuchu grows older,
        she starts becoming more active and playful. Chuchu does care for everyone around her, as
        seen with her meek behavior.
    </string>

    <string name="cat_about_coco">
        Coco is a white-coated Highland Straight. Coco has white colored fur with big sky blue eyes.
        He has fluffy fur and a fluffy tail. Coco usually appears to be very calm, but in the past
        he was a mischievous cat. Coco dislikes food with strange smells and even makes a face when
        strange food is moved closer to him. Coco is not vocal at all as he meows only few times.
        He is the most timid cat, as he easily gets nervous and uncomfortable when he is taken to a
        vet. Coco hates the camera for unclear reasons. His pupils would swell up when the camera is
        brought near to him and he even punches it before running away. Coco grew up to be a
        trouble-making and naughty teenager. However, with time, Coco lost his mischievous
        personality and became calm and nice.
    </string>

    <string name="cat_about_momo">
        Momo is a Garfield-faced Exotic Shorthair. His name also means peaches in Japanese. Momo
        has ginger/orange fur and yellowish eyes. His face look a bit grumpy when seen closely. He
        is also very tall and long. He is rather stocky built, with a roundish face. He loves
        playing with toys and shows dislike being groomed by others. Momo is a very mischievous cat,
        but he mellowed out as he got older. He is very soft and when receiving an injection in a
        cat hospital, he could easily slip away and needed to be held tightly without escaping. He
        is also very tall and long, as seen when he was stretched during an X-ray at the hospital.
        He also feels uncomfortable when getting his claws trimmed. He seems to have a good sense of
        balance and athleticism, as he is shown to leap high. Momo thinks too much before doing
        something in the games arranged for the cats, getting confused to the point that he even
        stops what he is doing.
    </string>

    <string name="content_desc_app_icon">Icon of the app</string>
    <string name="content_desc_row_cat_image">Picture of the cat.</string>
    <string name="content_desc_expand_cat_row_desc">Expand description of the cat.</string>
    <string name="content_desc_cat_detail_image">Banner of the cat.</string>
    <string name="content_desc_up_navigate_detail">Go back to cats list screen.</string>
    <string name="content_desc_cat_gender_picture">Picture which shows gender of the cat.</string>
    <string name="content_desc_picture_paw_puppy">Paw picture of the puppy.</string>
</resources>